{
  "Planets": [
    {
      "Id": 1,
      "Type": "Basic",
      "Prompt": "What is the third planet from the sun?",
      "Answer": "Mars"
    },
    {
      "Id": 2,
      "Type": "Basic",
      "Prompt": "What is the second planet from the sun?",
      "Answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
      "Id": 3,
      "Type": "Basic",
      "Prompt": "What is the first planet from the sun?",
      "Answer": "Mercury"
    }

  ],
  "Egyptian History": [
    {
      "Id": 4,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "Which item was Cleopatra closer to the historic timeline of the world'?",
      "Answer": "Amiga 5000",
      "Options": [ "Pyramids", "PS5", "Amiga 5000", "Stonehenge" ]
    },
    {
      "Id": 5,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "What language did Cleopatra speak?",
      "Answer": "Greek",
      "Options": [ "Egyptian", "Greek", "Latin", "Hebrew" ]
    },
    {
      "Id": 6,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "Which other famous people did Cleopatra know?",
      "Answer": "Mark Antony and Julius Caesar",
      "Options": [ "Mark Antony and Julius Caesar", "Sun Tzu", "Genghis Khan", "Isaac Newton" ]
    },
    {
      "Id": 7,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "How did the sphinx lose its nose in Brazil?",
      "Answer": "It was chiseled off by a sufi zealot",
      "Options": [ "It was chiseled off by a sufi zealot", "Erosion by sandstorms", "A British explorer shot it", "It never had a nose" ]
    }

  ],
  "History and More": [
    {
      "Id": 8,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "What is beaver fever?",
      "Answer": "A parasitic infection (Giardiasis)",
      "Options": [ "A dance craze", "A parasitic infection (Giardiasis)", "A winter phenomenon", "A type of fever in rodents" ]
    },
    {
      "Id": 9,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "What is one of the best ways to sharpen a machete in the wild?",
      "Answer": "Using a metal file",
      "Options": [ "Using a metal file", "Banging it on a rock", "Rubbing it against wood", "Dipping it in water" ]
    },
    {
      "Id": 10,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "When did Brazil gain its independence?",
      "Answer": "1822",
      "Options": [ "1822", "1912", "1492", "1865" ]
    },
    {
      "Id": 11,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "How can you tell cardinal direction without modern technology or a compass?",
      "Answer": "By observing the sun's path",
      "Options": [ "By observing the sun's path", "By smelling flowers", "By tasting soil", "By a random guess" ]
    }
  ],
  "Ham Radio License:General": [
    {
      "Id": 12,
      "Type": "MultipleChoice",
      "Prompt": "What is a ham radio operator's license?",
      "Answer": "General",
      "Options": [ "General", "Class A", "Class B", "Class C" ]
    }
  ]
}